{
    "id": "3f908d752d9a4a979d29417b2de5e74f",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If you knew the answer, why ..................... you tell me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "don't",
                "didn't",
                "hadn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If it ……………….. Jeena why didn’t she stop and say Hi?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you had listened to him, you ………………….. in trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "won't have landed",
                "wouldn't have landed",
                "wouldn't land"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If I know his name, I ……………….. you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would tell",
                "will tell",
                "would have told"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If she applied for that job, she …………………. it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will get",
                "would get",
                "would have got"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If she asked more politely, I ………………… her a few pounds.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will lend",
                "would lend",
                "would have lent"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If you …………………. you will get cancer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "smoke",
                "smoked",
                "had smoked"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "If she ..................... now, we would be in trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "arrive",
                "arrived",
                "had arrived"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Feel free to call me if you ……………….. any help.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "need",
                "needed",
                "would need"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………….. them if I had more time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would visit",
                "will visit",
                "would have visited"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}